# Jordan Jarvis

385-225-5058 | jj.mm.jj@hotmail.com | linkedin.com/in/jordan-jarvis-69825874 | github.com/Jordan-Jarvis

### **Summary Of Qualifications**

Highly motivated with a goal to develop groundbreaking technologies. Skills include: advanced logic, reasoning, coding, teamwork, and communication skills. Experience includes vision systems development, Machine Learning, high efficiency C++, computer science and algorithms, Linux administration, and 7 years of personal research in computer science.

### **Related Skills**

C++ (3 years), C# (2 years), Java (2 years), Python (3 years), VMWare (4 years), Hyper-V (4 years), Batch Scripting (4 years), Linux Development (3 years), Machine Learning (1 year), Computer Vision (1 year), TensorFlow (1 year), OpenCV (1 year), Node.js (1 year), SQL (2 years), OpenCV (1 year), familiar with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, Docker, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Flask, NumPy, RESTful APIs, React.js

#### **Education**

BS Computer Science | Brigham Young University - Idaho | Rexburg, Idaho

January 2018 - December 2020

- GPA: 3.64
- Related Coursework: Object Oriented Programming, Discrete Mathematics II, Algorithms and Complexity, Data Structures, Web Engineering I III, Calculus, Linear Algebra, Machine Learning, Operating Systems, Computer Architecture, Databases Oracle SQL, Computer Security, Software Engineering I-III

### **Projects**

- Developed a Sudoku and boggle solver using vision systems and machine learning with OpenCV and TensorFlow (140 hours)
- © Gained an understanding of data structures, various sorting algorithms, multi-threading/processing, low level memory manipulation, and machine learning algorithms in several Computer Science classes.
- Learned how to code in Batch and Powershell during slow phone traffic at Bask Corporation which led to a new position in Automation Scripting, allowing the company to save hundreds of man-hours.
- Developed a free C# toolkit to automatically root, unlock, lock, flash firmware, and perform various other modifications to a Xiaomi Mi A2 android phone including modification of operational wireless bands and kernel modification. (80 hours)
- Created RaspberryPi system to play and record midi files on a Disklavier piano including: Google home integration, phone controls, touchscreen interface at the piano and web controls. (160 hours)
- Created automation scripts and code while working as a First Responder at Equinox IT Services streamlining new system installs, resulting in a time saving of several man-hours per system.

### **Work Experience**

First Responder | Equinox IT | Orem, Utah

August 2017 - September 2018

- Solved complex problems regarding security, networking, backups, automation and more.
- Provided quality client interactions and coordinate team efforts for large projects.
- Installed Workstations, Servers, Network gear, and other business critical infrastructure.
- Designed systems to automatically detect system failures, attempt recovery, and notify respective teams proactively.

Help-desk Technician | Bask Corporation | Thanksgiving Point, Utah

November 2016 - August 2017

- Worked as a team to solve technical issues such as inbound calls and work anything from printers to viruses to slow computers, network setup and even smart home appliances.
- Automated workflows using batch and powershell.

Service Technician - Preventive Pest Control | First Responder - Equinox IT | Orem, Utah April 201

April 2016 - October 2016

Provided quality service to customers in addition to apply product to customers houses, identify and resolve pest issues in a professional manner.

## **Communication And Management Experience**

District Leader | The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints | San Diego, California

Service Mission and Humanitarian Aid

Acted as a District Leader during a 2-year service mission in San Diego. (2014-2016)

Team Worker | First Robotics | Salt Lake City, Utah

Competitive Robotics Competition

Designed and constructed a remote-controlled robot in an annual First Robotics Competition as part of a 10-member team.

Eagle Scout | Boy Scouts of America | Salt Lake City, Utah

Youth leadership and self reliance program.

Led over 50 men and women to complete a coordinated bike trail cleanup and associated necessary maintenance.